<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RENE HLAVOVA</title>
    <link>https://renehlavova.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on RENE HLAVOVA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://renehlavova.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Data Analytics</title>
      <link>https://renehlavova.com/portfolio/data_analytics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renehlavova.com/portfolio/data_analytics/</guid>
      <description>I come from social sciences background and my programming skills are self-learnt. Recently, I joined a team of data detectives in BizzTreat (2021 - today). Previous years, I worked for Kiwi.com (2019 - 2021), and Seznam (2021).
I am skilled in preparing data models (ETLs) in Keboola or Airflow, statistical analyses in Jupyter notebooks, dashboards in GoodData, Tableau, Looker or PowerBI, wrote a lot of SQL, and even played with some HTML and JavaScript when working with Retool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>https://renehlavova.com/portfolio/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renehlavova.com/portfolio/music/</guid>
      <description>I started playing piano at the age of 6 at a local art school. Over the years, I did gigs with two musical bands and performed in cafés around Brno (Czech Republic), but did not continue to study music professionally.
During psychology studies, my activities were still centered around music - I organized musical activities for child psychiatry patients, conducted a research project related to music and well-being in the elderly, or helped conceptualize music therapy studies at University of Ostrava.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://renehlavova.com/portfolio/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://renehlavova.com/portfolio/research/</guid>
      <description>As my main interest is tied to quantitative data analysis, statistics, and data science, I was a part of multiple projects with differing topics.
The latest news is a release of Psychology and Behavioral Economics (2021) textbook where I worked on two chapters, Education and behavior and Evidence-based policy. It is aimed to help get an idea how to use behavioural science in public policy.
Below, you can find other example projects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
